Guide to the National Coalition for Haitian Rights Records, 1964-2020, bulk 1982-2004 RL.11314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1964-2008, undated; bulk 1980-2006; 5; 89 boxes
  - Executive Director of International Civilian Mission to Haiti, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Executive Summary on Haiti - Electoral Observation Mission, 1995 (Box 97)
  - Exhumation project, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Exhumation training, 1992 (Box 97)
  - Experts meeting on Haiti Truth Commission, 1994 (Box 97)
  - Facts on farm workers and Haitians in farm work, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Factsheet on special agricultural workers, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Fair Housing and Community Integration (incl. Scholarly articles, reports, and press), 1986-2008; 1 of 2 (Box 97)
  - Fair Housing and Community Integration (incl. Scholarly articles, reports, and press), 1986-2008; 2 of 2 (Box 97)
  - FAIR Immigration Report, 1992 (Box 149)
  - FAIR press releases, 1992 (Box 149)
  - Fair Treatment of Haitian Refugees, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Family Youth Community Research Center, undated (Box 97)
  - Farm workers in Florida, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Farmworker Justice News Vol. 4 No. 1, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Father Adrien notes, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Father Gerard Jean-Juste, 1983-1985 (Box 97)
  - Fauntroy Protest, 1989 (Box 97)
  - Fax from CIDIHCA on 1991 coup d'état (Box 97)
  - Fax to Steven Koutsis, 1991 (Box 97)
  - FDA blood ban, 1990 (Box 147)
  - FDA treatment of Haitian refugees, 1990 (Box 97)
  - Federation of Peasants of Laveje Saut-d'Eau report, 1991 (Box 150)
  - Feminine Committee on the Struggle Against Torture, 1986 (Box 98)
  - Fenelon Jean, 1994 (Box 98)
  - First Asylum Refugee Assistance Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 98)
  - FLACSO (Facultad Latinoamericana de Ciencias Sociales), 1996 (Box 98)
  - Florida Rural Legal Service, Inc., 1993 (Box 98)
  - Florida, California, etc., 1996-1998 (Box 98)
  - FNCD, 1987 (Box 98)
  - FNCD about the arrest of KID, 1990 (Box 132)
  - FNCD statement, 1991 (Box 98)
  - FOIA Request, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Forced Migration, 1998 (Box 98)
  - Ford Foundation, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee to Secretary of State, 1989 (Box 98)
  - Formation and Development New Sovereign Nation on the Island of Tortuga - Lund International, 1989 (Box 152)
  - Francine Marshall to McCalla, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Franck Romain Affair, 1989 (Box 98)
  - French Evangelical Church of New York, 1990 (Box 148)
  - Frères sans Frontières, 1988 (Box 98)
  - Friends of Haiti Statement of Conclusion, 1993 (Box 150)
  - Fund for an Open Society, 2008 (Box 98)
  - Gail Spain to NCHR, 1993 (Box 98)
  - GAO Report - Embargo Violation, 1992 (Box 98)
  - GAO Reports - on shipments in Haiti, 1992 (Box 98)
  - General Assembly for the Safety of Children and World Movement in Favor of Children in Haiti, 2001 (Box 98)
  - George Crockett, 1987 (Box 149)
  - George Izmery, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Gerard Gourge to Lafoutant Joseph, 1987 (Box 98)
  - Gerard J. Pierre, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Gilles Dauroc Communications, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Giuliani to Rev. Anthony J. Bevilacqua, 1982 (Box 98)
  - Giuliani on immigration, 1989 (Box 98)
  - Giuliani to Michael Posner, 1982 (Box 98)
  - Giuliani to Posner, 1982 (Box 146)
  - Global exchange Haiti Update, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Gotz-Dietrich Opitz dissertation on Haitian refugee crisis, 1995 (Box 98)
  - Gov. Clinton's Message to Haiti, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Government in Exile Materials - Haiti, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Government/Business partnership conference on Haiti, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Governors Island Accord, NY Pact and related material, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Governors Island Reinforcement Act of 1994 (Box 98)
  - Governor's Island Watch - update faxes, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Graham Amendment, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Gretta Tovar's Memo Re: Mission to Study In-Country Processing in Haiti, 1993 (Box 98)
  - GROHE presents its complements to E.P. Trouillot, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Group of 12 documents, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Group of 12 news articles, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Groups to Observe Haiti's election, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Guantanamo - "Political Asylum Project for Haitians Screened in Guantanamo Bay", 1992 (Box 98)
  - Guantanamo - "Safe Haven" and Guantanamo, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Guantanamo - affidavits and statements from Haitians in Guantanamo Bay, 1995; 1 of 2 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - affidavits and statements from Haitians in Guantanamo Bay, 1995; 2 of 2 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - affidavits from Guantanamo Bay, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Asylum Pre-Screening, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Guantanamo - Bureaucracy, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Conference on the aftermath of Guantanamo, 1993 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - contrition for the homeless Guantanamo Bay refugees, 1993 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Correspondence/letter to Jean Bertrand Aristide from Louis Ronald and Faniel Francois i.e.: Guantanamo, 1993 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Correspondence/letters from Guantanamo Bay, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - draft- "Guantanamo Bay is a Detention Camp, not a Safe Haven", 1991 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Guantanamo Bay contact list, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Guantanamo Bay Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Guantanamo Bay Daily Stat Reports, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Guantanamo Refugee Project- situation report, 1994 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Guantanamo Refugee project World Relief weekly report, 1995 (Box 99)
  - Guantanamo - Haitian Refugees in Guantanamo, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Haitian Refugees in Guantanamo, 1994 (Feb - June) (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Haitian Refugees in Guantanamo, 1994 (July - Sep) (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - information from Guantanamo Bay visit, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - NCHR statement on conditions in Guantanamo, 1991 (Box 151)
  - Guantanamo - notices on Guantanamo Bay repatriations, 1995 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Political asylum project for Haitians paroled from GTMO naval base, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - pregnant HIV+ women at Guantanamo Bay, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Preliminary Assessments of Haitians Paroled through Guantanamo, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Refugees in the US, undated (Box 146)
  - Guantanamo - Report on Haitian Detainees in Guantanamo, 1994 (Box 150)
  - Guantanamo - reports from Guantanamo refugee project, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Request the Administration to Comply with Expected Court Order on Guantanamo Haitians, 1993 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Rules and legislations for Guantanamo visitors, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Secretary of Defense, support/donations for Haitians at Guantanamo Bay, 1991 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - staff correspondence on weekend Guantanamo trip, 1993 (Box 151)
  - Guantanamo - Stanley Urban affidavit on Guantanamo, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Temporary protection process in Guantanamo, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - Testimony of an interpreter in Guantanamo, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Guantanamo - US Policy towards Haitian Unaccompanied Minors at Guantanamo, 1995 (Box 100)
  - Guy Beauduy, 1998 (Box 100)
  - Guy Malary, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Guyana Human Rights report, 1990 (Box 100)
  - H.R. 4264- Conyers Bill, 1994 (Box 101)
  - H.R. 4300 and the Legal Immigrant Debate, 1990 (Box 101)
  - H.R. 5360 International Refugee Protection Act of 1992 (Box 151)
  - HAEDA- Haitian American Education and Development Association, 1993 (Box 101)
  - Haiti - various reports and articles, 1995; 1 of 2 (Box 149)
  - Haiti - various reports and articles, 1995; 2 of 2 (Box 149)
  - Haiti (USCC) notes, undated (Box 117)
  - Haiti aid groups meetings, 1995 (Box 125)
  - Haiti and Immigrants (news articles), 1998-2000 (Box 101)
  - Haiti by department (maps), 1992 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Communications Project, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Communications Project statement of purpose, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Haiti correspondence #26, 1993 (Box 151)
  - Haiti Country Programme Assessment Mission, 2004 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Demonstration folder, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Disaster Relief, 1998-1999 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Disaster Relief Committee, 1998 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Disaster Relief Committee, 1998 (Box 101)
  - Haiti D'outre Mer Alliance, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Fundraising Entity, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Haiti GDES custom report, 1996-1997 (Box 101)
  - Haiti insight, 1996 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Legislation Update HCHR fax, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Lumiere, 2001 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Media directory, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Haiti meetings, 1994-2004 (Box 117)
  - Haiti museum of national resistance, 1996 (Box 101)
  - Haiti National Congress on Democratic Alternative, 1986 (Box 101)
  - Haiti National Network, 1992; 1 of 2 (Box 101)
  - Haiti National Network, 1992; 2 of 2 (Box 101)
  - Haiti National Network, 1997 (Box 101)
  - Haiti NGO draft interview guide, 1995 (Box 149)
  - Haiti press briefing, 1995 (Box 151)
  - Haiti Primer, 2003 (Box 101)
  - Haiti refugees, various print materials, 1995 (Box 101)
  - Haiti report CIA?, 1987 (Box 101)
  - Haiti resolution project, 1989 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Solidarite Internationale Profect, 1987 (Box 149)
  - Haiti Solidarity Committee on Refugees, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Haiti Solidarity International, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Solidarity International, 1989 (Box 101)
  - Haiti Solidarity International, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Haiti Solidarity week, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Haiti timeline, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Haiti trip, 1993 (Box 151)
  - Haiti truth commission, 1996 (Box 102)
    [French, Spanish]
  - Haiti truth commission, 1995 (Box 102)
  - Haiti Truth Commission memos, 1994 (Box 149)
  - Haiti Truth Committee meeting minutes, 1994 (Box 102)
  - Haiti US Aid, 1989 (Box 132)
  - Haiti, Labor US Jobs, 1983-1984 (Box 102)
  - Haiti: Challenge of Restoring Human Rights and Democracy (Center for International Policy), 1993 (Box 102)
  - Haiti: Resistance and Democracy- Daily Information Bulletin, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Adjustment cases, 1988 (Box 148)
  - Haitian Aid articles, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Haitian American Community Action Network, 1997 (Box 102)
  - Haitian American Community Action Network- News and Updates, 1997 (Box 102)
  - Haitian American Community Organizations, undated (Box 102)
  - Haitian American Foundation, 1990 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Army by Jocelyn McCalla, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Haitian Army Personnel, 1994 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Campaign, 1998; 1 of 2 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Campaign, 1998; 2 of 2 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Center for Family Services (HCFS), 2001 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Center for Human Rights- interviews with detainees, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Center for Human Rights organizational summary, 1984 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Center for Human Rights to Ira Gollobin, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Center for Human Rights to Pax Christi USA, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Creole Summer Institute, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Haitian Crisis Protocol, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Dateline - Concepts, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Haitian diaspora community, 2000 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Disaster Relief Committee, 1998 (Box 103)
  - Haitian environment problems, 1989 (Box 71)
  - Haitian Fairness Act, 1997-1998; 1 of 2 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Fairness Act, 1997-1998; 2 of 2 (Box 103)
  - Haitian foreign minister meeting, 1991 (Box 117)
  - Haitian government correspondence, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Haitian groups in Boston List, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Haitian History and Culture, 1987 (Box 103)
  - Haitian human rights groups petition, 1990 (Box 147)
  - Haitian human rights groups petition to end US violations of international law, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Haitian human rights news, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Haitian immigration files, 1992-1995 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Information and Documentation Center, Inc. by-laws, 1983 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Initiative on Environment, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Interdiction Program report - draft, 1989 (Box 149)
  - Haitian Judicial System UN Assessment Recommendation, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Lawyers Committee project, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Lawyers Committee report, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Lawyers Committee to McCalla, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Lawyers Committee to McCalla, 1989 (Box 103)
  - Haitian Lawyers Leadership Conference, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Migrant Populations, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian military deserters to President Clinton, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Haitian National Network (HNN) meeting materials, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Neighborhood Family Resource, 2000 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Officers enrolled in armed forces, 1989 (Box 116)
  - Haitian officers list, 1991 (Box 116)
  - Haitian Organization of Women (HOW), 2001 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Organization: Immigration Welfare Citizenship as of 11/11/97, 1997 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Organizations Denise Singh report, 1991 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Organizations for Human Rights, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Organizations to Bush, 1991 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Action Alert, 1992 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Advocacy Update, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian refugee aid brochures, 1985 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Campaign, 1992 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center, 1991 (Box 132)
  - Haitian Refugee Center documents, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center faxes on "VolReps", 1994 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center letters, 1994 (Box 151)
  - Haitian Refugee Center Statement and funding proposal, 1981 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center to Chip Gardner, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center to Penny Rivkind, 1989 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Center to Senators, 1991 (Box 152)
  - Haitian Refugee Fairness Act, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Fairness Act of 1993 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Immigration Fairness Act, 1998 (Box 104)
  - Haitian Refugee Policy Proposal, 1992 (Box 104)
  - Haitian refugee status, 1992 (Box 149)
  - Haitian refugees, 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - Haitian refugees - press, contacts, undated (Box 105)
  - Haitian refugees correspondence, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Refugees Protection Act, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Haitian refugees testimonies, 1995 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Refugees: A Proposal for Temporary Safe Haven, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Haitian reports/articles, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Resource Consortium International, Inc. Annual Report, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Haitian resource groups, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Retainees Miami, 2002 (Box 105)
  - Haitian rice farmers, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Haitian sayings and concepts, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Haitian State council's mandate, 1990 (Box 132)
  - Haitian Student Associations, 2004 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Studies Association, 1993 (Box 117)
  - Haitian Studies Association - minutes, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Studies Association Creole Summer Language Institute, 1995 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Studies Association Steering Committee and conference materials, 1989-1991 (Box 105)
  - Haitian support, 1998 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Unaccompanied Minor Conference LIRS-USCC, 1992 (Box 105)
  - Haitian United for Progress, 2000 (Box 105)
  - Haitian Women of Miami, 1995 (Box 105)
  - Haitian-American political action committee (NOHAP), 1993 (Box 105)
  - Haitians Americans United for Progress, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 105)
  - Haiti-Lutte Weekly Magazine, 1992-1993 (Box 105)
  - Haiti-Profile of Asylum Claims and Country conditions, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Haiti's speech at OAS, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Half-Measures press release, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Hansruedi Peplinski and excerpt of UN Human Rights Commission Report, 1989 (Box 149)
  - Hansruedi Peplinski of Lutheran World Federation, 1988 (Box 149)
  - HAPAG- Grassroots Advocacy, 1994 (Box 105)
  - Harry Belafonte to President Clinton re: Haiti Refugee Democracy, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Harvard Law School- Haiti Asylum Claims, 1992; 1 of 3 (Box 151)
  - Harvard Law School- Haiti Asylum Claims, 1992; 2 of 3 (Box 151)
  - Harvard Law School- Haiti Asylum Claims, 1992; 3 of 3 (Box 151)
  - Harvard Law School Immigration Clinic, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Harvard study- Sanctions in Haiti, 1993 (Box 105)
  - HAS - L'Association des Etudes Haïtiennes, 1996 (Box 105)
  - Hasruedi Peplinski to Mike Hooper, 1987 (Box 149)
  - HAVA - Haitian Association of Volunteer Agencies, 1990 (Box 105)
  - HAVA Meeting Packet, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Healthcare in Haiti proposal, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Hearing- democracy in Caribbean, 1991 (Box 106)
  - Helene Lauffer to Jewel Lafontaint, 1990 (Box 106)
  - Helet Merkling, 1992 (Box 106)
  - HIAS Action Report, 1990 (Box 106)
  - HIAS annual report, 1984 (Box 106)
  - HIV - "HIV and Immigrants Do Not Threaten Public Health", 1993 (Box 106)
  - HIV - African Jesuit AIDS Network meeting notes, 2002 (Box 106)
  - HIV - African Jesuit AIDS Network travel documents, 2002 (Box 106)
  - HIV - AIDS Blood Ban protest coverage, 1990 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Brooklyn AIDS Task Force- proposal on HIV and Haitian refugees, 1993 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Correspondence/letter re: offensive line in "How Stella Got Her Groove Back" re: Haiti and AIDS, 1998 (Box 106)
  - HIV - FDA-AIDS notes, 1990 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Haitian refugees: figures, processes (incl. when HIV positive) sample application, 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - HIV - HIV Exclusion and changes in Medical Exam for Immigrants, 1991 (Box 150)
  - HIV - HIV fraud, 1995 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Information manual on AIDS, 1994 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Latino Commission on AIDS, 1996 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Lavi Nouvo (New Life): A Musical Play, Haitian Teens Confront AIDS, undated (Box 106)
  - HIV - Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Correspondence/letter on HIV and Refugees, 1993 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Legalization: AIDS testing, 1987 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Material for protest against Guiliani's decision to act Division of AIDS Program, 1994 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Prison Camps, 1992 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Proposal for Research Project on HIV, 1991 (Box 106)
  - HIV - Rally for HIV prisoners at pre-trial hearing, 1992 (Box 106)
  - HIV - summary of HIV+ case processing, 1994 (Box 106)
  - HIV and refugees articles (Box 147)
  - HMP hemispheric migration project, 1988 (Box 106)
  - Honorat to Col. Duperval, 1990 (Box 106)
  - House Judiciary Committee, 1988 (Box 149)
  - House of Representatives Resolution, 1991 (Box 106)
  - How to… guide (Haitian Community in NYC), 1985 (Box 106)
  - Howard French to Ann Fuller, 1992 (Box 106)
  - Howard French to Jocelyn McCalla, 1990 (Box 148)
  - HRC forces DFD status for Haitians in the US, 1994 (Box 106)
  - HRC screening, 1992 (Box 147)
  - HRC to McCalla, 1993 (Box 106)
  - HRC to members of Congress, 1992 (Box 106)
  - HRC to Representative Fascell, 1990 (Box 147)
  - HRW proposed policy statement, 1990 (Box 106)
  - HUDC report, 1990 (Box 106)
  - Human Alliance, 1989 (Box 106)
  - Human rights abuses, 1992 (Box 106)
  - Human Rights Advocacy to President Clinton, 1994 (Box 106)
  - Human Rights and Economic Development: A Syllabus, 1987 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights groups correspondence, 1990 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights groups in Haiti - thank you letter, 1987 (Box 148)
  - Human Rights Groups on repatriation, 1993 (Box 107)
  - Human rights groups to OAS, 1991 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights in Belize, 1989 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights in China, 1993 (Box 107)
  - Human rights in Haiti since the 1991 coup d'état (binder incl. declarations, bulletins, press, etc.), 1991-1992 (Box 107)
  - Human rights memo, 1990 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights missions in El Salvador, Cambodia and Haiti assessment, 1994 (Box 151)
  - Human Rights Packet, 1988; 1 of 2 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Packet, 1988; 2 of 2 (Box 107)
  - Human rights projects, 1993 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Report, 2002 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights situation in Haiti [h], 1992 (Box 107)
  - Human rights violations in college environments, undated (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Violations in Haiti, 1992-1993 (Box 107)
  - Human rights violations in Haiti- report, 1990 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Watch Americas (memos), 1994 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Watch Comment on US State Department, 1991 (Box 150)
  - Human Rights Watch correspondence, 1994 (Box 107)
  - Human Rights Watch report overview, 1989 (Box 107)
  - Hunger Strike by Haitian Detainees in Laredo TX, 1990 (Box 150)
  - Hunger Strike for Haiti, 1994 (Box 150)
  - HURIDOC news, 1991 (Box 107)
  - Ian Martin to Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1994 (Box 107)
  - ICITAP records in Haiti, 1995 (Box 107)
  - ICM Assessment Lawyers Committee, 1994 (Box 107)
  - ICP Preliminary Questionnaire, undated (Box 107)
  - ICVA, 1989 (Box 107)
  - ICVA Commission on Humanitarian Affairs Geneva, 1994 (Box 107)
  - ICVA mission to Haiti description, 1994 (Box 150)
  - Ignacio Martin- Baro Fund for Mental Health and Human Rights, 1994-1995 (Box 107)
  - IIDH conference packet, 1991 (Box 107)
    [French] [Spanish] [Kreyol]
  - IIDH to McCalla, 1991 (Box 152)
  - IL GWU letter/article, 1991 (Box 151)
  - Ileana Ros-Lehtinen to Frank Young, 1996 (Box 108)
  - ILOP Meeting notes, 1993 (Box 108)
  - IMED: "Politics in Haiti", 1989 (Box 108)
  - IMED: Proposal, 1987 (Box 108)
  - IMED press release, 1986 (Box 108)
  - IMED proposals, 1988 (Box 108)
  - IMED: reflection on the human rights situation in Haiti, 1989 (Box 108)
  - Immigrant departure list, 1992 (Box 108)
  - Immigration Act Implementation Task Force, 1991 (Box 108)
  - Immigration Act Task Force info, 1991 (Box 117)
  - Immigration Forum, 1993 (Box 108)
  - Immigration Law News, 1993 (Box 108)
  - Immigration related documents, 2002 (Box 108)
  - Implementation- Latin American refugees, 1987 (Box 108)
  - Improving prison conditions in Haiti, 1992 (Box 108)
  - Improving Prison's Conditions in the Caribbean, 1991 (Box 116)
  - Independent Monitoring project, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Index of regions of Haitian immigrants, 1983 (Box 108)
  - Individual affidavits and statements, 1976 (Box 108)
  - Individual testimonies on human rights situation in Haiti [h], 1992 (Box 108)
  - Information Ministry - ban of "Regime de Facto" turn, 1992 (Box 108)
  - Information on Asylum Seekers, 1992 (Box 108)
  - Information on the NGO Washington Office on Haiti, 1990 (Box 108)
  - Ingrid Harris- Complaints review information, undated (Box 108)
  - INMED, 1992 (Box 108)
  - INS Asylum Reform Plan and Proposed Regulations, 1994 (Box 109)
  - INS info packet, 1992 (Box 109)
  - INS prepared summaries of interview, 1991 (Box 109)
  - INS report: a brief history of Post-Duvalier Haiti, 1986-1990 (Box 109)
  - Insecurity Chronicle (ANOP), 1988-1989 (Box 109)
  - INS-Memo on Refugee Processing, 1993 (Box 109)
  - Institute for Human Rights and Responsibilities, 2000 (Box 109)
  - Institutionalizing Human Rights in Haiti, 1998 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Commission for Human Rights report, 1999 (Box 149)
  - Inter-American Commission on Human Rights abuses in Haiti, 1996 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Commission on Human Rights press release, 1990 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Committee statement, 1990 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Foundation, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Foundation, 1991 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Foundation "Background on Crisis in Rural Haiti", 1991 (Box 109)
  - Inter-American Institute of Human Rights, 1990 (Box 148)
  - Inter-American Press Association, 1992 (Box 109)
  - Interfaith Community Services, 1998 (Box 109)
  - International Aid to Haiti and Slavin article, 1991 (Box 109)
  - International Alliance for Haiti press release, 1989 (Box 109)
  - International Civil Mission of Haiti, 1994 (Box 132)
  - International Civilian Mission in Haiti, 1993 (Box 109)
  - International Civilian Mission in Haiti, 1995 (Box 109)
  - International Conference on Democratic Transitions, 1995 (Box 109)
  - International Human Rights Law Group, 1993 (Box 109)
  - International Human Rights Law Group faxes, 1993 (Box 109)
  - International Human Rights Law Groups to President Clinton re: detention of Haitian asylum seekers in Texas and Louisiana, 1993 (Box 109)
  - International Human Rights Law Groups to Judge Hubbell, 1993 (Box 109)
  - International immigrants foundation, 1991 (Box 109)